John and Susan Edwards Harvith Interview Collection
John and Susan Edwards Harvith Interview Collection
1998-2001
Harvith, John.; Harvith, Susan Edwards.
1.5 linear ft
Audio and video recordings of interviews by the Harviths of important figures in the history of the arts and the history of radio and television, including actors, conductors, directors, musicians, writers, producers, and others.
4089759
Biographical History
John Harvith and Susan Edwards Harvith are mass communications and arts historians who together have produced exhibitions and film series, as well as books and articles. Their research has emphasized the interface between the arts and technology in film, photography, radio, and television, resulting in numerous interviews with cinematographers, film editors, musicians, and radio and television pioneers.
Scope and Contents of the Collection
The John and Susan Edwards Harvith Interview Collection consists of interviews with over sixty important figures -- actors, comedians, musicians, writers, directors and producers -- in the history of radio and television broadcasting, particular comedy and drama. These interviews, conducted primarily in the subject's homes, offer unique personal insights into the heyday of broadcast television, what it was like to be involved in massively popular television shows of the time, and how American popular culture shaped and was shaped by them. Television shows represented include Father Knows Best, All in the Family, M*A*S*H*, I Love Lucy, and many more.
Other Formats Available
All audiocassettes save the interview of Dr. and Mrs. Rose Setnor (harvith_int_131) have been digitized as of March 27, 2017.
Arrangement of the Collection
Alphabetical by last name of person being interviewed.
Related Material
has numerous collections relating to music, entertainment, and television and radio broadcasting history. Please for a complete listing.
Subject and Genre Headings
Popular culture; Radio, television, film; Music; Actors -- United States.; Actresses -- United States.; Comedians -- United States.; Conductors (Music) -- United States.; Dancers -- United States.; Musicians -- United States.; Pianists -- United States.; Radio broadcasting -- United States -- History.; Radio comedy writers -- United States.; Radio personalities -- United States.; Radio writers -- United States.; Singers -- United States.; Television broadcasting -- United States -- History.; Television comedy writers -- United States.; Television personalities -- United States.; Television producers and directors -- United States.; Television writers -- United States.; Women comedians -- United States.; Audiocassettes.; Sound recordings.; Interviews.
Access Restrictions
The majority of our archival and manuscript collections are housed off site and require advanced notice for retrieval. Researchers are encouraged to contact us in advance concerning the collection material they wish to access for their research.
Access to videotape and undigitized recordings requires advance notice for production of a listening copy.
Acquisition Information
Gift of John Harvith and Susan Edwards Harvith.
Inventory
- Interviews
  - Eddie Albert, parts 1 and 2, 01/10/2000; harvith_int_001; interview with actor Eddie Albert, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Eddie Albert, parts 3 and 4, 01/10/2000; harvith_int_002; interview with actor Eddie Albert, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Eddie Albert, part 5, 01/10/2000; harvith_int_003; interview with actor Eddie Albert, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Arthur Alsberg, parts 1 and 2, 08/08/2000; harvith_int_004; interview with radio comedy writer Arthur Alsberg; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Arthur Alsberg, parts 3 and 4, 08/08/2000; harvith_int_005; interview with radio comedy writer Arthur Alsberg; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Martina Arroyo, 05-01-1977; harvith_int_130; interview with American soprano, Martina Arroyo; 1 1/2-inch videotape (Box 4)
  - Bea Arthur, parts 1 and 2, 01/05/2000; harvith_int_006; interview with television and film actress Bea Arthur, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Bea Arthur, part 3, 01/05/2000; harvith_int_007; interview with television and film actress Bea Arthur, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Conrad Bain, parts 1 and 2, 05/06/1999; harvith_int_008; interview with actor Conrad Bain, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Kaye Ballard, parts 1 and 2, 08/04/2000; harvith_int_009; interview with Kaye Ballard, musical theatre and television actress, comedienne and singer; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Kaye Ballard, part 3, 08/04/2000; harvith_int_010; interview with Kaye Ballard, musical theatre and television actress, comedienne and singer; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Gary Belkin, parts 1 and 2, 01/09/2000; harvith_int_011; interview with Gary Belkin, writer for comedy and variety shows, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Gary Belkin, part 3, 01/09/2000; harvith_int_012; interview with Gary Belkin, writer for comedy and variety shows, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Milton Berle, parts 1 and 2, 08/02/1999; harvith_int_013; interview with comedian Milton Berle at the Friars Club; "in the Milton Berle Room, Rocky Kalish in attendance", in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Milton Berle, parts 1 and 2, 01/17/2000; harvith_int_014; interview with comedian Milton Berle, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Milton Berle, part 3, 01/17/2000; harvith_int_015; interview with comedian Milton Berle, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Frans Brüggen at Rackham, 03/22/1977; harvith_int_128; interview with Dutch conductor, recorder player and flautist, Franciscus Brüggen; 1 1/2-inch videotape (Box 4)
  - Betty Folker Bullock, 08/02/2000; harvith_int_016; interview with Betty Folker Bullock, wife of television and film writer Harvey Bullock; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Harvey Bullock, parts 1 and 2, 08/02/2000; harvith_int_017; interview with Harvey Bullock, television and film writer; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Harvey Bullock, parts 3 and 4, 08/02/2000; harvith_int_018; interview with Harvey Bullock, television and film writer; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Harvey Bullock, parts 5 and 6, 08/02/2000; harvith_int_019; interview with Harvey Bullock, television and film writer; also includes his wife Betty Folker Bullock; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Sid Caesar, parts 1 and 2, 05/03/1999; harvith_int_020; interview with Sid Caesar, comic actor and writer, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Sid Caesar, parts 1 and 2, 05/03/1999; harvith_int_021; interview with Sid Caesar, comic actor and writer, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Bob Carroll, Jr., See Madelyn Davis and Bob Carroll, Jr..
  - Hal Cooper, parts 1 and 2, 07/29/2000; harvith_int_022; interview with director Hal Cooper; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Hal Cooper, parts 3 and 4, 07/29/2000; harvith_int_023; interview with director Hal Cooper; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Hal Cooper, parts 5 and 6, 07/29/2000; harvith_int_024; interview with director Hal Cooper; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Hal Cooper, parts 7 and 8, 07/29/2000; harvith_int_025; interview with director Hal Cooper; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Hal Cooper, parts 9 and 10, 07/29/2000; harvith_int_026; interview with director Hal Cooper; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Hal Cooper, parts 11 and 12, 07/29/2000; harvith_int_027; interview with director Hal Cooper; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Jackie Cooper, parts 1 and 2, 01/09/1999; harvith_int_028; interview with Jackie Cooper, actor, television director, producer and executive; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Jackie Cooper, parts 3 and 4, 01/09/1999; harvith_int_029; interview with Jackie Cooper, actor, television director, producer and executive; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Norman Corwin, parts 1 and 2, 01/16/2000; harvith_int_030; interview with Norman Corwin, writer, screenwriter, producer, essayist and teacher of journalism and writing, at Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Norman Corwin, parts 1 and 2, 01/16/2000; harvith_int_031; interview with Norman Corwin, writer, screenwriter, producer, essayist and teacher of journalism and writing, at Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Madelyn Davis and Bob Carroll, Jr., parts 1 and 2, 07/31/1999; harvith_int_032; interview with Madelyn Davis (also known as Madelyn Pugh Davis, Madelyn Pugh, or Madelyn Martin) and Bob Carrol, Jr., television comedy writers and creators of I Love Lucy, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Madelyn Davis and Bob Carroll, Jr., parts 3 and 4, 07/31/1999; harvith_int_033; interview with Madelyn Davis (also known as Madelyn Pugh Davis, Madelyn Pugh, or Madelyn Martin) and Bob Carrol, Jr., television comedy writers and creators of I Love Lucy, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Elinor Donahue, parts 1 and 2, 05/07/1999; harvith_int_034; interview with actress Elinor Donahue, at Chez Nous restaurant, in North Hollywood, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Jack Elinson, parts 1 and 2, 07/30/2000; harvith_int_035; interview with Jack Elinson, writer and producer for television comedy; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Jack Elinson, parts 3 and 4, 07/30/2000; harvith_int_036; interview with Jack Elinson, writer and producer for television comedy; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Jack Elinson, part 5, 07/30/2000; harvith_int_037; interview with Jack Elinson, writer and producer for television comedy; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Robert Ellenstein, parts 1 and 2, 01/11/1999; harvith_int_038; interview with actor Robert Ellenstein; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Robert Ellenstein, parts 3 and 4, 01/11/1999; harvith_int_039; interview with actor Robert Ellenstein; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Robert Ellenstein, part 5, 01/11/1999; harvith_int_040; interview with actor Robert Ellenstein; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Nanette Fabray, parts 1 and 2, 01/16/1999; harvith_int_041; interview with Nanette Fabray, actress, comedienne, singer, dancer, and activist; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Nanette Fabray, part 3, 01/16/1999; harvith_int_042; interview with Nanette Fabray, actress, comedienne, singer, dancer, and activist; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Nanette Fabray, parts 1 and 2, 05/04/1999; harvith_int_043; interview with Nanette Fabray, actress, comedienne, singer, dancer, and activist, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Nanette Fabray, part 3, 05/04/1999; harvith_int_044; interview with Nanette Fabray, actress, comedienne, singer, dancer, and activist, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Betty Garrett, parts 1 and 2, 07/28/1999; harvith_int_045; interview with Betty Garrett, actress, comedienne, singer and dancer, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Betty Garrett, parts 3 and 4, 07/28/1999; harvith_int_046; interview with Betty Garrett, actress, comedienne, singer and dancer, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Betty Garrett, part 5, 07/28/1999; harvith_int_047; interview with Betty Garrett, actress, comedienne, singer and dancer, in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 1)
  - Larry Gelbart, parts 1 and 2, 07/21/1999; harvith_int_048; interview with Larry Gelbart, television writer, playwright, screenwriter and author, and creator and producer of M*A*S*H., in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Larry Gelbart, parts 3 and 4, 07/21/1999; harvith_int_049; interview with Larry Gelbart, television writer, playwright, screenwriter and author, and creator and producer of M*A*S*H., in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Bill Gray, parts 1 and 2, 01/06/1999; harvith_int_050; interview with actor Bill Gray (William Thomas Gray); 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Bill Gray, parts 3 and 4, 01/06/1999; harvith_int_051; interview with actor Bill Gray (William Thomas Gray); 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Guarneri Quartet, 1977; harvith_int_127; interview with Guarneri Quartet (Arnold Steinhart - 1st violin, John Dailey - 2nd violin, Michael Tree - viola, and David Soyer, Violoncello); 1 1/2 inch videotape (Box 4)
  - Kitty Carlisle Hart, parts 1 and 2, 08/00/1999; harvith_int_052; interview with Kitty Carlisle, singer and actress; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charles Isaacs, parts 1 and 2, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_053; interview with radio and television comedy writer Charles Isaacs; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charles Isaacs, parts 3 and 4, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_054; interview with radio and television comedy writer Charles Isaacs; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charles Isaacs, parts 5 and 6, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_055; interview with radio and television comedy writer Charles Isaacs; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charles Isaacs, parts 7 and 8, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_056; interview with radio and television comedy writer Charles Isaacs; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charles Isaacs, parts 9 and 10, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_057; interview with radio and television comedy writer Charles Isaacs; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charles Isaacs, parts 11 and 12, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_058; interview with radio and television comedy writer Charles Isaacs; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Sheldon Keller, parts 1 and 2, 01/10/2000; harvith_int_059; interview with Sheldon Keller, screenwriter and composer, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Don Knotts, parts 1 and 2, 07/26/1999; harvith_int_060; interview with actor Don Knotts, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Norman Lear, parts 1 and 2, 01/13/2000; harvith_int_061; interview with Norman Lear, television writer and producer, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Janet Leigh, parts 1 and 2, 08/01/2000; harvith_int_062; interview with actress Janet Leigh (Jeanette Helen Morrison); 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Janet Leigh, parts 3 and 4, 08/01/2000; harvith_int_063; interview with actress Janet Leigh (Jeanette Helen Morrison); 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Art Linkletter, parts 1 and 2, 01/15/2000; harvith_int_064; interview with radio and television personality Art Linkletter (Gordon Arthur Kelly), in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Art Linkletter, parts 3 and 4, 01/15/2000; harvith_int_065; interview with radio and television personality Art Linkletter (Gordon Arthur Kelly), in California; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Adrienne Luraschi, parts 1 and 2, 08/03/2000; harvith_int_066; interview with television producer and director Adrienne Luraschi; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Adrienne Luraschi, parts 3 and 4, 08/03/2000; harvith_int_067; interview with television producer and director Adrienne Luraschi; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Kevin McCarthy, parts 1 and 2, 01/15/2000; harvith_int_068; interview with actor Kevin McCarthy, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Kevin McCarthy, part 3, 01/15/2000; harvith_int_069; interview with actor Kevin McCarthy, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Howard Morris, parts 1 and 2, 07/30/1999; harvith_int_070; interview with actor and director Howard Morris, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Howard Morris, parts 3 and 4, 07/30/1999; harvith_int_071; interview with actor and director Howard Morris, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - David Nelson, parts 1 and 2, 01/12/2000; harvith_int_072; interview with David Nelson, actor, director, and producer.; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - David Nelson, part 3, 01/12/2000; harvith_int_073; interview with David Nelson, actor, director, and producer.; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Don Nelson, parts 1 and 2, 08/08/2000; harvith_int_074; interview with Don Nelson, screenwriter, film producer and musician, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Don Nelson, part 3, 08/08/2000; harvith_int_075; interview with Don Nelson, screenwriter, film producer and musician, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Louis Nye, parts 1 and 2, 01/15/1999; harvith_int_076; interview with comedy actor Louis Nye; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Louis Nye, parts 3 and 4, 01/15/1999; harvith_int_077; interview with comedy actor Louis Nye; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Ted Post, parts 1 and 2, 08/06/2000; harvith_int_078; interview with Ted Post, television and film director and producer; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Ted Post, parts 3 and 4, 08/06/2000; harvith_int_079; interview with Ted Post, television and film director and producer; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Ted Post, parts 5 and 6, 08/06/2000; harvith_int_080; interview with Ted Post, television and film director and producer; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Tom Poston, parts 1 and 2, 05/05/1999; harvith_int_081; interview with actor Tom Poston, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Tom Poston, part 3, 05/05/1999; harvith_int_082; interview with actor Tom Poston, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Charlotte Rae, parts 1 and 2, 07/23/1999; harvith_int_083; interview with Charlotte Rae (Charlotte Rae Lubotsky), actress, singer, dancer and comedienne, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - John Randolph, parts 1 and 2, 01/13/2000; harvith_int_084; interview with actor John Randolph, in Hollywood, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - John Randolph, part 3, 01/13/2000; harvith_int_085; interview with actor John Randolph, in Hollywood, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - John Randolph, parts 1 and 2, 01/16/2000; harvith_int_086; interview with actor John Randolph, in Hollywood, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - John Randolph, part 3, 01/16/2000; harvith_int_087; interview with actor John Randolph, in Hollywood, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Carl Reiner, parts 1 and 2, 07/20/1999; harvith_int_088; interview with Carl Reiner, actor, film director, producer, writer, and comedian, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Carl Reiner, part 3, 07/20/1999; harvith_int_089; interview with Carl Reiner, actor, film director, producer, writer, and comedian, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Gene Reynolds, parts 1 and 2, 07/27/1999; harvith_int_090; interview with Gene Reynolds, actor, television writer, director, and producer, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Gene Reynolds, parts 3 and 4, 07/27/1999; harvith_int_091; interview with Gene Reynolds, actor, television writer, director, and producer, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Gene Reynolds, part 5, 07/27/1999; harvith_int_092; interview with Gene Reynolds, actor, television writer, director, and producer, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Larry Rhine, parts 1 and 2, 08/12/2000; harvith_int_093; interview with Larry Rhine, comedy writer for radio, television and film; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - Larry Rhine, part 3, 08/12/2000; harvith_int_094; interview with Larry Rhine, comedy writer for radio, television and film; 1 audiocassette (Box 2)
  - John Rich, parts 1 and 2, 01/14/2000; harvith_int_095; interview with film and television director John Rich, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - John Rich, parts 3 and 4, 01/14/2000; harvith_int_096; interview with film and television director John Rich, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - John Rich, parts 5 and 6, 01/14/2000; harvith_int_097; interview with film and television director John Rich, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - John Rich, parts 7 and 8, 01/14/2000; harvith_int_098; interview with film and television director John Rich, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - John Rich, parts 1 and 2, 08/01/2000; harvith_int_099; interview with film and television director John Rich; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - John Rich, parts 3 and 4, 08/12/2000; harvith_int_100; interview with film and television director John Rich; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Aaron Ruben, parts 1 and 2, 01/11/2000; harvith_int_101; interview with television director Aaron Ruben, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Aaron Ruben, parts 3 and 4, 01/11/2000; harvith_int_102; interview with television director Aaron Ruben, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Aaron Ruben, parts 5 and 6, 01/11/2000; harvith_int_103; interview with television director Aaron Ruben, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Aaron Ruben, parts 7 and 8, 01/11/2000; harvith_int_104; interview with television director Aaron Ruben, in Beverly Hills, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Joseph Ruskin, parts 1 and 2, 07/23/1999; harvith_int_105; interview with actor Joseph Ruskin, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Joseph Ruskin, parts 3 and 4, 07/23/1999; harvith_int_106; interview with actor Joseph Ruskin, in Annette Kaufman's home, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - György Sándor, harvith_int_132; interview with Hungarian born pianist and writer, György Sándor; 1 1/2 inch videotape (Box 4)
  - William Schallert, parts 1 and 2, 07/27/1998; harvith_int_107; interview with actor William Schallert; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - William Schallert, parts 3 and 4, 07/27/1998; harvith_int_108; interview with actor William Schallert; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - William Schallert, parts 5 and 6, 07/27/1998; harvith_int_109; interview with actor William Schallert; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf, parts 1 and 2, 01/08/2000; harvith_int_110; interview with television writers Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf, in Santa Monica, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf, parts 3 and 4, 01/08/2000; harvith_int_111; interview with television writers Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf, in Santa Monica, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf, parts 5 and 6, 01/08/2000; harvith_int_112; interview with television writers Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf, in Santa Monica, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Dr. Jules and Mrs. Rose Setnor, 10/09/1997; harvith_int_131; interview with Dr. Jules and Rose Setnor; 1 audiocassette (Box 4)
  - Doris Singleton, parts 1 and 2, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_113; interview with actress Doris Singleton; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Doris Singleton, part 3, 08/10/2000; harvith_int_114; interview with actress Doris Singleton; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Jean Stapleton, parts 1 and 2, 11/03/2000; harvith_int_115; interview with actress Jean Stapleton; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Jean Stapleton, part 3, 11/03/2000; harvith_int_116; interview with actress Jean Stapleton; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - János Starker, 03/14/1977; harvith_int_128; interview with Hungarian-American cellist, János Starker; 1 1/2-inch videotape reel (Box 4)
  - Leonard Stern, parts 1 and 2, 07/21/1999; harvith_int_117; interview with Leonard Stern, film and television producer, writer and director, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Leonard Stern, parts 3 and 4, 07/21/1999; harvith_int_118; interview with Leonard Stern, film and television producer, writer and director, in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Mel Tolkin, parts 1 and 2, 07/24/1999; harvith_int_119; interview with television comedy writer Mel Tolkin (Shmuel Tolchinsky), in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Mel Tolkin, parts 3 and 4, 07/24/1999; harvith_int_120; interview with television comedy writer Mel Tolkin (Shmuel Tolchinsky), in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Mel Tolkin, parts 5 and 6, 07/24/1999; harvith_int_121; interview with television comedy writer Mel Tolkin (Shmuel Tolchinsky), in Los Angeles, CA; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Bob Weiskopf, See Bob Schiller and Bob Weiskopf.
  - Earl Wild, parts 1 and 2, 06/04/2001; harvith_int_122; interview with pianist Royland Earl Wild, in Columbus, OH; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)
  - Jane Wyatt, parts 1 and 2, 07/24/1998; harvith_int_123; interview with actress Jane Wyatt; 1 audiocassette (Box 3)